

Senior Digital Product Designer | UX/UI, Web, Html & CSS, Mobile, Motion Graphics, Social Videos

ABOUT ME

I'm about researching client and user/market needs and creating dynamic digital messaging and products by strategically using CTA's, typeface, colour and layouts/ wireframes that put user experience and user interface at the forefront.

> UX/UI portfolio

Click to view

I'm a designer & I code HTML and CSS portfolio Social Videos portfolio

Click to view

Motion Graphics and

Click to view

More on my webpage: https://edwinau.github.io/edwin-landing <a href="https://edwinau.github.io/edwinau.github.

WORK EXPERIENCE

■ Borden Ladner Gervais LLP

Senior Designer | Digital & Multimedia **⊘** Jan 2020 - Present **¬** www.blg.com



- > Collaborate in the creation of company webpages for BLG.com and BLG Beyond; while applying best UX/UI practices, responsible for balancing speed, quality, and consistency of design with meeting firm objectives
- > Researching client and market needs and applying best site nav usage and webpage wireframes to determine optimized page patterns for best UX/UI results
- > Responsible for providing final web assets including hero banners; inline animated graphics and infographs; and adjusting page responsiveness for Desktop and Mobile experiences by injecting custom HTML and CSS code
- > Providing social media assets including digital Linkedin posts, social videos, gifs and more

Blake, Cassels & Graydon LLP

Designer | Motion Graphics, Web, HTML





- > Heavy involvement in the launch of blakes.com from user research, site nav and working with wireframes; to providing final visual web assets including landing page banners, homepage animated banners, inline graphics and infographs, headshots, graphics for hover state flip tiles, and more
- > Working with HTML and CSS templates to facilitate client event eVites, working with CRM, B2B clients, spam filters and CASL compliance
- > Providing social media assets for LinkedIn, Twitter, Facebook, Instagram and Youtube
- > Providing assets for digital event signage, newsletters and internal communications as required

≥ Disney Consumer Products

Consumer Product Designer Nov 2013 - Mar 2016



- > Provided creative guidance in the design and development of Disney Branded Consumer Products sold across Walmart Canada, Target Canada, Canadian Tire, Toy R' Us, Dollarama, Uniglo and more
- > Working with the team in leading 50+ licensees on 300+ products simultaneously and seasonally. Work days range from managing online product design approvals, to meeting with vendors communicating design goals and initiatives

Dolce & Gabbana (Milan, Italy)

Intern Sep 2012 - Oct 2013



SKILLS



Sketch























EDUCATION

✓ Master Classes (IDF)

Storytelling Through Visual Design: with Ellen Lupton | Jan 2022

> Exploring visual design principles for desktop and mobile experiences through the exploration of storytelling and user journeys

General Assembly

Web Development Program Mar 2017 - Jun 2017

- > Web Dev Immersive Full Stack Program with UX/UI experience
- HTML5, CSS3, Sketch, Figma, JavaScript, Ruby, Rails, jQuery, AJAX, SQL, SASS

Toronto Metropolitan University

B.A.A. - Fashion Design Degree Sep 1998 - Apr 2002

- Product Design, Graphic Design, Marketing, Trend Analysis
- Fashion Communication with focus in R&D, working in agile environments

Birmingham City University (UK)

Merchandising and Design Jan 2001 - Aug 2001

- Selected by Ryerson University to partake in the London, UK exchange program
- Thesis: Triple P bottom line and relation to green design